Brandon Czaja

Chicago, IL | (603)540-3182

https://brandon-czaja.vercel.app/ | Brandon.Czaja@gmail.com | github.com/BrandonCzaja

Personal Statement:

I am a team-oriented, goal-driven, full stack developer experienced in JavaScript, Ruby on Rails, Django, and React, with a side passion for history. I love programming because it is a lot like history; individual lines of code may seem small and insignificant, but each line has a unique impact on the larger program, similar to events in our own lives. Those events develop us into who we are, just like each line of code shapes the program.

SKILLS:

Full Stack Development | JavaScript | ES6 | Express | jQuery | Node.js | HTML5 | CSS3 | JWT Authentication | React | MongoDB | Mongoose | Ruby | Ruby on Rails | Postman | PostgreSQL | SQL | API Requests | Flexbox | Git | GitHub | Heroku | Python | Django | React Native | Vercel | Gatsby | Bootstrap | Jira

Other Professional SKILLS:

Adobe Acrobat | Fork Truck License | Formally licensed in Series 6 and Series 63

PROJECTS:

Board Game Collection: https://digital-shelfie.herokuapp.com/

September, 2020

- A database app that allows users to login, search for board games, and add them to their collection
- Technologies Used: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JS, JQuery, Express, React, MongoDB, Mongoose, Heroku

Magic The Gathering Card Search App: - https://magic-the-gathering-card-and-set-search.vercel.app/

August, 2020

- A searchable app that allows users to search for individual cards and view entire set's Card Image Galleries
- Technology Used: HTML, CSS, JS, JQuery, API Requests, Vercel

•

Group Project: Ubuntu - I am because we are: https://practical-jones-b55cd9.netlify.app/

October, 2020

- A full CRUD application that allows users to improve their communities with community oriented events
- Technologies Used: Bootstrap, Express, Flexbox, JWT Authentication, Milligram, Mongoose, Node.js, Postman, React

WORK EXPERIENCE:

Art Institute of Chicago - Museum Specialist

February, 2016 - January, 2021

- Lead exhibition installations and manage collection storage spaces
- Manage database of art collection to determine inventory and schedule maintenance and exhibition changes
- Track and manage art database through the shipment and meticulously documenting packing procedures
- Maintain department inventories and heavy equipment service log to reduce cost of replacing essential tools.

Isabella Stewart Gardner Museum - Collection Maintenance Technician **Lincoln Financial Group** - Investment Services Administrator

March, 2015 - February, 2016 January, 2012 - August, 2014

EDUCATION:

- General Assembly: Software Engineering Immersive Certificate, Sololearn.com Certificate in JavaScript
- Tufts University: Graduate Certificate in Museum Studies
- Southern New Hampshire University: Bachelor of Arts in History